Goals

I am a former architect, I have always enjoyed the diverse expressions of human nature, the reason why I later reached to interpretation and translation studies. I strongly believe in the values that diversity brings to our daily interactions, promoting mutual understanding and tolerance and making stronger communities. I enjoy new challenges that allow me to use my education, skills and experience towards the continuous improvement of our society, bridging the gap between cultures and languages, being positive always goes to others!

Education

- Bellevue College, Translation and Interpretation Certification (Present).
- American Sign Language (Basic).
- WAAC Virginia Tech, Architecture. Scholarship Aug 2008- Jan2010.
- UNAM Architecture, Mexico City 2013.

Qualifications

- Seven years of Customer Service Experience.
- Interpersonal communication, collaboration, team player.
- Native Spanish Speaker, bicultural competence.
- Excellent organizational skills, scheduling, problem solving, locating resources.
- Social media proficiency and advanced computer skills.
- Volunteer translator for The Hope Heart Institute and EMP now MoPOP museum.

Experience

- Amazon.com, August 2016-Present, Downtown Seattle, WA. Seller Support Associate, World-class customer support to Amazon Sellers in North America Region, we work to eliminate any challenges and pain points that sellers may face when selling their products on Amazon's platform.
- Nintendo of America, October 2014-Present, Redmond WA. Bilingual Customer Service Representative (Intake/consumer contact, email correspondence).
- NeighborCare Health at Columbia City, April-August 2016. Bilingual Patient Service Representative. Front desk staff, Scheduling, Call Center, Administrative Support, Interpreting.
- Universal Language Service, Inc. Interpreter, August 2015-Present. Medical; Healthcare; Behavioral Health; Rehabilitation, Drug, and Alcohol; Rehabilitation, Vocational; Protective Services, Adult, and Children; Socio-Economic Benefits; Employment; Law Enforcement; General; Business, Marketing; Education; Others (Noncertified, yet).
- RPM (Receivables Performance Management), September 2014, Lynwood WA. Bilingual Agent.
- Gustavo Ayala Architecture, 2013 Mexico City. Construction Supervisor Assistant.
- Zara Mexico, 2013, Mexico City. Retail and Fashion advisor.
- Tecnovidrio, 2012, Mexico City. Construction Materials Sales Advisor.
- Patanegra Nightclub, 2012, Mexico City. Hostess and Cashier.
- Aero Mexico, 2011-2012, Mexico City. Customer Service Representative. at International Airport, Ticketing/gate.